[music]
>> anticipated
smaller than anticipated
highly anticipated as anticipated
supervise
supervise the night shift closely
supervise supervise a team
inventory
refresh inventory
take inventory current inventory
fundraiser
upcoming fundraiser host a fundraiser
fundraiser gala
sponsor
major sponsor potential sponsor
corporate sponsor
replacement
replacement batch seek a replacement
replacement parts
maintenance
down for maintenance
routine maintenance maintenance
department
remotely
edit files remotely
work remotely
access remotely
sensitive sensitive information
sensitive data
time-sensitive
unauthorized
unauthorized access unauthorized use
unauthorized personnel
orientation
orientation session orientation program
employee orientation
troubleshooting troubleshooting tips
troubleshooting manual troubleshooting
process
customized customized services
customized cleaning
customized solution
shuttle
shuttle bus
downtown shuttle complimentary shuttle
reasonable
reasonable price
reasonable request reasonable excuse
opportunity
rare opportunity
take advantage of career opportunity
wholesale
wholesale supplier wholesale price
wholesale market
nationwide
appear nationwide nationwide
distribution available nationwide
recognition
recognition reward in recognition of
gain recognition
schedule ahead of schedule
behind schedule
working schedule
revitalize
revitalize the district revitalize the
economy
revitalize a brand
temporary
temporary situation temporary position
temporary closure
deficit slight deficit budget deficit
trade deficit
periodical
expensive periodical
monthly periodical subscribe to a
periodical
reschedule
reschedule an appointment reschedule a
meeting forced to reschedule
expedite
expedite a delivery
expedite the process
expedite a request
wave wave a production charge wave a
fee, wave a requirement.
Exceed.
Budget exceeded, exceed expectations,
exceed the limit.
Advantage. Take advantage of,
competitive advantage, distinct
advantage.
Operation.
Hours of operation, daily operations,
standard operating procedure.
Budget.
Balance the budget, within budget,
marketing budget.
Repair.
Perform minor repairs, repair shop,
under repair.
Promote. Promote the opening, promote an
event, promote a product.
Excitement.
Build excitement, generate excitement,
sense of excitement.
Advertisement.
Run text advertisements, online
advertisement, mention an advertisement.
Action plan.
Complete the action plan, develop an
action plan, implement an action plan.
Workstation.
Placement of a workstation, ergonomic
workstation, shared workstation.
Defect. Without the defect, product
defect, manufacturing defect.
Durable.
Durable and attractive, durable
materials, highly durable.
Boutique. Partner with boutique stores,
boutique hotel, boutique agency.